<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eline Lund</title>
    <link>https://elinelund.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eline Lund</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 17:18:11 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://elinelund.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book: Rethinking Education</title>
      <link>https://elinelund.github.io/posts/rethinking_education/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 17:18:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elinelund.github.io/posts/rethinking_education/</guid>
      <description>Title: Rethinking Education: Whose knowledge is it anyway?
Authors: Adam Unwin and John Yandell (Institute of Education, University College London)
Year: 2016
This little book raises some big questions in education: What is the point of school? Is technology the answer? To what extent is the imposition of a curriculum on learners justifiable? Can assessment be objective and reliable? Do schools reduce or increase inequality? What kind of education could be possible?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Development Goals: activities for globally connected and locally responsible classrooms</title>
      <link>https://elinelund.github.io/posts/sustainable_development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 17:18:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elinelund.github.io/posts/sustainable_development/</guid>
      <description>In 2015, the UN launched the Global Sustainable Development Goals, a series of ambitious targets to end extreme poverty, fight inequality and injustice and fix climate change for everyone by 2030.
In early 2015, Project Everyone and UNICEF began to collaborate on an idea to teach children across the world about the new Global Goals. They called it the World’s Largest Lesson.
Since then, classrooms around the globe have taken on the mission to support these goals through local projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>